A mutant virus has emerged
in which patients begin
to exhibit symptoms within five minutes
in low-pressured environments.
A much faster pace compared to
previous incubation period of 24 hours.
Raising even greater concerns
in regards to containment.
After the outbreak,
the increase of symptoms
like abnormal physical ability
and violent tendencies
has led the infected
to display animal-like behaviors,
making it difficult
to secure quarantine facilities.
In the United States, more than
150,000 people have been infected,
mostly by US forces
returning home from serving in Korea,
and more than 30,000 have died.
North Korea is on the verge of collapse
with over eight and a half million
reported infected people,
representing a third
of the country's total population.
By contrast,
South Korea has just been declared
a DMZ Virus-free zone
by the World Health Organization today
when the last known infected person
known only as "Choi"
died after a thirteen-day illness.
To date, South Korea
has reported 345 total cases with 34..
Go.
MOTEL
Team Two, supporting the site.
Team Three, blocking the exit.
The cause of the DMZ Virus
which was allegedly
first detected in the DMZ,
a symbol of the ceasefire between
North and South Korea, ten months ago,
has not yet been identified.
It has been 19 days since Dr. Jung
and his daughter have disappeared
while on their way to North Korea,
and there is no information
about their whereabouts.
Dr. Jung became quite famous,
after curing his daughter Ha-na
of the DMZ virus,
drawing the attention
of academics worldwide.
Dr. Jung had been en route to the
Sinuiju Chemical Weapons Institute
in order to mass produce
the antibody treatment,
as was agreed upon
by both North and South Korea,
when he disappeared
along with his daughter.
Some organizations accused
the South Korean government
of putting on a show
in order to cripple
the North Korean infrastructure,
and warned that demonstrations
demanding the whereabouts of Dr. Jung
and his daughter,
as well as their return to North Korea,
would take place nationwide.
Opposing organizations
heavily criticized them,
labeling them as pro-North Korean,
accusing them of working
for the North Korean government,
and warned of a counter demonstration.
As a result, police are on high alert
to keep the situation
from getting violent..
Who are you?
Where is Dr. Jung Byeong-ho?
Doctor? Who is that person?
Where did you get this?
Where is Dr. Jung Byeong-ho?
Why are you asking me this?
Watch this.
Dr. Jung is with me at the moment.
If you come to the Possess Motel
room 605 in Yeongdeungpo market,
you can meet him.
This is what you sent.
The man in this video
is me?
What have you done
to the back of your head?
Before we blast your head off,
answer me correctly!
I can't remember anything.
I can't even remember my name.
Whose blood is this?
Answer the phone.
Answer the phone, now!
Hello?
Your name is Carter.
"Carter"?
What is "Carter"?
I'd like to speak
with the person behind you.
Could you please put them on the phone?
She'd like to... to speak with you.
Answer.
Who is this?
We're going to blow up
this room in 20 seconds.
That will lure in
the rest of their forces.
Who are you? How are you talking to me?
What happened?
What the hell is
this guy rambling on about?
There is a device implanted
in your ear.
You are the only one who can hear me.
Jump out of the window
to get to the next building.
Please trust me, if you want to live.
Ten seconds left.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five...
Carter.
Carter, are you okay?
What is this place?
What is it
that you're looking at?
- So you're Korean then?
- Is that what matters right now?
Listen to me if you want to live.
Sir, help me. Wait.
These assholes are completely insane.
Don't worry
about the people there,
just get out of that building quickly.
Who are you?
Me?
What, we introducing ourselves now?
I didn't mean you.
When they arrive, you'll die before
you can get your questions answered.
Who are "they"?
Why don't you tell me
who the hell you are first, huh?
CIA.
"CIA"?
CIA? So you're here now,
to save me, right?
- The CIA?
- I thought that I was a goner.
Are we sure we got the right guy?
- Sorry.
- What are you doing?
Wait. Come on. Murder these bastards!
Hey, what are you waiting for, huh?
No, that's not me.
Hold him!
Kill!
Yah!
- Over there!
- Kill him!
Over there!
- He's going down!
- Get him!
Hyah!
There he is! Get him! We want him alive!
The market is right in front
of you. Go in that direction.
The other side!
Go out the other side
of the market and turn left.
What in the world...
Someone's on my tail.
50 meters in front of you,
you'll see a Papa John's motorcycle.
Use it to escape.
Stop that man!
He's getting on a bike!
Stop him! Stop him! Cut him off!
Move!
He's going down! Get him!
Carter. Go to
the back door of the clothing shop.
Call the police!
Please, please, come on, hurry.
- Come on, hurry. Please.
- What do I say?
Yes, I'm at a clothing store.
A strange man...
You'll find a staircase
at the end of the left passage.
Go upstairs.
How do you know all this?
I can get
the security camera information
and the blind spots from your earpiece,
which can detect heat signatures
in your fifty-meter radius.
Carter!
A target with a CIA frequency
is approaching.
Eliminate him
and secure his device.
The CIA is all over the place.
Hide somewhere, now.
Secure the device on his wrist.
We're going to backtrace their hideout.
"Backtrace"?
There's a car approaching
at the end of the alley.
Get in the car and hand over the device.
Tell me why the CIA is chasing me.
There's a lethal bomb
planted in your mouth.
It has blast radius of ten meters.
If you refuse to work with us,
it will activate.
License plate 4566.
Your questions will be answered
once you get into the car.
And why would I get in that car?
Tell me, now.
Then you give us no choice.
You must be terminated.
I have the detonator here in my hand.
The car is approaching.
Move it. And hurry.
Is Hye-won doing well in class?
DAEHAN TAEKWONDO
- Drive! Drive!
- Over there!
You have the device?
- Hack it.
- Right. I'll start tracing them.
Choi Yu-jin, NIS.
Strategic relations with North Korea.
And the woman talking in my ear,
she on your side?
I'm Han Jung Hee.
I work for
the International Liaison Department
of the Labor Party in North Korea.
We are currently working with South Korea
to create a treatment for the DMZ Virus.
These are North Koreans
who have been infected by the DMZ Virus.
The infected
are overwhelmingly strong and violent.
Some have been discovered
to even be able to use tools or weapons.
All of South Korea's army is at the DMZ,
holding off the infected,
but every day is precarious.
In North Korea,
we have secured
a hundred million anthrax vaccines
needed to produce the treatment,
as well as a large scale assembly line,
so that Dr. Jung's research
can be carried out smoothly.
That's the reason we tried to bring
Dr. Jung and his daughter, Jung Ha-na,
to the North
for the completion of the project.
Daughter?
Dr. Jung's daughter was infected
by a field rat
while they were living out in Paju.
He was able to cure his own daughter,
and started studying her antibodies
to find a treatment.
However, due to an abnormal increase
in thromboplastin,
an enzyme that coagulates blood
once it leaves the body,
her antibodies were
destroyed in seconds.
That's why we were heading to
the Sinuiju Chemical Weapons Institute,
for Ha-na's blood.
However, Ha-na was kidnapped
on her way to North Korea
by an agent from A9,
a secret organization in the CIA.
Your mission is to find Ha-na
and bring her to North Korea.
You're the one who
suggested this mission.
It was your idea.
Why would I?
You commanded us to
block the memory center in your brain.
Am I your commander?
I suppose you'll return
to your position
after the mission is finished.
Why would I erase my memory,
and give up my rank?
You used to be
a CIA agent from South Korea,
but you disguised yourself as a reporter
and entered North Korea.
You became a hero to our people.
You were a hero to South Korea.
However, the North Korean government was
suspicious that you were an American spy
and assigned a woman
to keep a close eye on you.
The two of you fell in love,
and even got married.
And then, you had a daughter.
This woman and I?
But your wife died
from the DMZ Virus,
and your daughter, Yoon Hee,
also got infected
and is now imprisoned
in the research facility in Sinuiju.
This is a good shot.
Look over here.
Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee!
Dad? Dad?
Dad...
- ...Dad.
- Yoon Hee.
That scar
on the back of your hand
is from the burn that
you got that night.
The weapons you need
for the infiltration are in here.
Now you can do what Han Jung Hee says
until the assignment is complete.
You need to save Ha-na
so that your daughter,
Lee Yun Hui, might live.
Go to the rooftop.
Ha-na is being held in the building
across from this one.
Check the weapons in the bag
and put them on.
We must move Ha-na today
if we want to save your daughter's life.
She doesn't have much time left.
The majority of those infected
die just under 13 days.
Today is the 13th day
since your daughter was infected.
How do I know
that child is really my daughter?
When you
get your memory back,
and your daughter is dead,
who will you blame?
Go through the door to your right
and move to the edge of the rooftop.
I've hacked the communication channels
of the CIA agents in the building.
I'm getting their whereabouts now.
Negative, sir.
We're still working on establishing
the identity of the subject.
Bullshit! Get the geeks
at Langley on it if you have to.
I can't do shit
until we have actual evidence
that the North is on the move.
The agents are gathered in
the motel you were in. Now is the chance.
FLORAL SUPPLIES WHOLESALE MARKET
The elevator control room is
through the door in front of you.
Move toward it.
I'm detecting the heat signature
of one adult
near the elevator on the ninth floor
and two on the seventh floor.
This mall looks out of business.
It's the perfect place
for the CIA to set up a temporary base.
The agents that were sent to the motel
are on their way back. Hurry.
And Ha-na?
I'm detecting
the heat signature.
I'm detecting her on the sixth floor.
Ha-na will be in the playroom
once you go through the emergency exit.
The heat signatures
near the entrance are targets.
EMERGENCY EXIT
Who are you? Why are you here?
Stay back! Stay away from me!
Ha-na? You're Ha-na, right?
- Listen, I'm..
- Stay back I said!
What should I do?
Hand her the phone.
Here, answer it.
I'll stay over here. Hmm?
Um, hello?
Dad? Dad, please, where are you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Dad, can I trust this man?
Okay, I'll do that.
Okay.
Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Let's go find your dad.
How though? How do we get out of here?
Get back! Get back!
You are a hard man to find, Mr. Lee.
Carter Lee.
That is your name, isn't it?
Oh, we're playing that game now.
That's fine.
Fortunately for us, I have a shit-ton
of computer geeks back at Langley
who get a boner whenever I ask
them to dig up some shit on people.
Between you and me,
they're probably a bunch
of introverted perverts who
couldn't do four push-ups
to save their life. But, uh,
they get the job done. So, you know,
what are you gonna to do?
All right, let's see here.
"Carter Lee. Born in 1986.
Jamsil, South Korea."
"Immigrated to New York at age 11."
Blah, blah, blah.
Some more boring shit.
Oh, damn!
You went to Sornell?
My cousin went there!
Yeah!
He was a real piece of shit.
Oh, okay, here we go.
2014, you traveled to North Korea
as a journalist and, uh...
What?
You become
a naturalized citizen of the DPRK?
Oh!
I bet it was
all of that socialist bullshit
they taught you back at Sornell.
Am I right? Huh?
A real hero of the people.
Yeah.
So,
here's the thing I don't understand,
and, uh, maybe you can help me out this.
What the fuck
are you doing back in South Korea?
And more importantly,
why are you fucking up my shit?
All right.
So check this out, man. I...
I actually don't give a fuck about you.
I.. I really don't.
Just tell me who you're working for.
And, uh... we'll call it a day.
Huh?
Is it the North?
Is it the South?
Come on. You can tell Smith Hyeong.
The North or the South.
What does it matter?
Oh, shit.
You can talk!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Please, continue.
At least they aren't the ones
watching people die from the virus.
And treating it as an opportunity.
So you're saying
the United States...
You think those 300,000
pissed off Koreans out there,
feel the same way?
I don't know,
I think they're pretty convinced
that this is all a fabricated scheme
formed by the South Korean government!
"Fabricated"?
Didn't you create that rumor
to incite a riot?
"Rumor"?
Us?
Oh, wow.
Carter.
The things they led you to believe...
Have you ever considered the possibility
that it could be
even more blinding
of the truth?
The real truth?
Sir!
What is it?
The CCTV results came in.
The movement of Carter Lee matches
that of former CIA Agent Michael Bane
by 87%.
Michael Bane...
Wasn't he KIA in Syria
in your last deployment together?
Yes, sir.
They told us he was dead,
but none of us had
actual eyes on his remains.
The fuck are you doing?
BD-7...
That's how
they successfully wiped his memory.
Maybe.
But I don't think they fully
reconstructed the new one quite yet.
The eyes...
You can change the face,
but not the eyes.
And they never lie.
Is this why you rushed back to Korea?
We'll have the answers
once we've run the DNA lab, sir.
The commies are getting cute.
Run it.
Sir.
What the hell's going on?
Hang tight, hero.
Who knows?
Maybe the results will tell me
that you're not as useless as I thought.
Sir! There's a signal
coming from the subject's body.
Scan it.
Carter!
I need to cut communication
from your ear piece for a moment
and use the signal in your molar
as a decoy.
Picking up a strange signal
coming from his molar, sir.
What the fuck are you waiting on?
Take it out!
Get off me! Get off!
Just open your mouth.
The molar will detonate in five seconds.
Get on my back.
Hold tightly onto me.
Ha-na!
- Mister, help!
- Ha-na, hang on just a second!
Mister, help!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Hey, are you all right?
What are you doing? This is my work van..
- Go, go, go!
- He's taking off!
Get him!
Repatriate
Dr. Jung to North Korea!
Repatriate! Repatriate!
We know
the US is behind all this!
We know! We know!
Repatriate
Dr. Jung to North Korea!
Repatriate! Repatriate!
We know
the US is behind all this!
We know! We know!
Repatriate
Dr. Jung to North Korea!
Repatriate! Repatriate!
Ha-na, what's wrong?
We know! We know!
Ha-na! Ha-na!
Dad.
Dad!
To North Korea!
We know! We know!
Dad!
Ha-na.
Do you know how worried I've been?
Where have you been?
- Huh?
- Ha-na. What's wrong?
We know! We know!
My dad is over there...
But that's not me.
He's with some other girl...
Repatriate! Repatriate!
We know
the US is behind all this!
We know! We know!
But why are people wearing masks
of me and my dad?
Repatriate! Repatriate!
Well, it's because
they want you to stay safe.
We know! We know!
Should we put them on too?
Repatriate! Repatriate!
We know
the US is behind all this!
We know! We know!
We bring you breaking news.
Dr. Jung,
who had been missing until now,
has been confirmed to be in Sinuiju.
We've just received a video
showing Dr. Jung himself.
Let us take a look.
Hello. I am Jung Byeong-ho.
And I have arrived safely to Sinuiju,
thanks to the North
and South Korean governments.
I have also spoken to my daughter
on the phone moments ago
and I plan to start developing a cure
as soon as possible...
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH JUNG BYEONG-HO
once I make it to
the Sinuiju Institute as planned.
Also, I have heard rumors
that the South Korean government
is attempting to destroy the North
right now.
However, I assure you it is not true.
Please do not be misled.
That was a video of
Dr. Jung sent directly from Sinuiju.
We will be reporting the rest on our
regular scheduled news. Thank you.
This should be good enough.
One year anniversary song.
Three, two, one.
- No! He can't.
- What?
- You're terrible at writing songs.
- Yeah, I can't.
Wait, try again...
Carter, why did you stop?
Ha-na is a little tired.
- I'm fine..
- Shh.
The van is approaching
across the street. Hurry.
DAEHAN TAEKWONDO
What?
Carter is heading towards the bus
with Ha-na!
Carter. Where are you going?
Follow my instructions.
I'm detecting the movements
of CIA agents nearby.
Carter! Why are you getting on a bus
all of a sudden?
Get off the bus!
Listen to my instructions. Carter!
I think the CIA has
caught on to your van.
If you don't follow my
orders, you and your daughter will both-
I've blocked the signal
to the device in your ear, Mich...
Agent Bane.
Why are you calling me Michael Bane?
It's time you tell me
who you really are.
Someone who knows you better
than that voice in your ear.
Yeah? What makes you so sure?
There was a time
where we faced life and death, together.
I'm on your side, Mike. I always was.
My side?
Your men just tried
to kill me back there.
And you expect me
to believe that you're on my side?
You really don't remember us?
I still see you...
In your eyes, I...
I just know you're still there.
I just know it's you.
Never mind.
It doesn't matter
if you remember me or not.
The DNA test will prove
that you're Michael Bane.
And until then, our agency
will continue to hunt you down.
You have to trust me
if you want to survive.
Yeah?
I've been hearing that a lot lately.
Fine. It's time you know
who they really are.
What's going on?
You still can't get a signal to Carter?
Someone's blocking
the communications channel.
First, let me identify the woman
who approached Carter.
The South is manipulating
the traffic lights.
The bus will stop 50 meters ahead
for one minute.
- Then we will be in range for the shot.
- Take her down.
We can identify her first,
there'll be time to take her out after.
Fire!
Run, Mike. Run before my men get here.
Hurry,
hurry, hurry, hurry!
She got shot!
Call an ambulance!
Mister!
Hold on tight! Careful!
We all saw
the lab results! Hold your fire!
That's Michael Bane!
It doesn't matter who he is.
He's gone rogue.
We have to take him out.
It's not his fault.
He's just being used by the people
that are really pulling the strings.
Yeah, well, that puppet
is about to kill Paul!
Requesting permission to engage.
Please,
sir, don't do this.
Take the shot.
Mister, please help me!
Mister!
Use the bus, block him!
Hold your fire!
Checking DNA now.
Plan B. Surround him.
There is an emergency
military airstrip at the end of the road.
A plane is waiting there
to take you to North Korea.
My name is Kim Dong-gyu, Director
of North Korean Relations at the NIS.
I am responsible
for getting you to North Korea safely.
We opened a communications
channel in the South as well.
You've done well.
Hey, Jung Hee?
I don't think he trusts me.
Director Kim will be
ensuring your safety during the flight.
Come on. Let's board.
The reporters will hassle you.
Don't say a thing.
Don't look at them either.
Keep looking forward.
Even your slightest movement, Agent Lee,
may put this country
could put Dr. Jung and South Korea
in a dangerous spot.
Is it true that Ha-na's...
We'll be flying with US reporters.
Reporters will be on board?
Yes, that way,
the entire world will be watching us.
It'll keep the US government
from acting so reckless.
How did you find her?
Please cooperate, as this was a choice
to ensure our safe arrival.
Jung Ha-na, kidnapped
daughter of Dr. Jung Byeong-ho,
reappeared today.
Now, the South Korean government
gave no statement
regarding the kidnapping itself,
merely making a statement that reuniting
the doctor with his daughter
is of the utmost priority.
We will keep you updated
on further developments in this story,
which will hopefully result
in Ha-na's safe return to North Korea.
Hey now, you
shouldn't smoke with a child on board.
Hey, look,
there's no need to be so uptight.
You will be staying
here as we make our way to North Korea.
Here, this way.
Hey, you gotta be Ha-na.
Ha-na.
Come on, all right?
To start, you should both see our medic.
TREATMENT ROOM
Hello. Welcome.
If you'll remove that,
we can start the treatment.
You can take that seat.
The plane is taking off soon.
Excuse me,
we have an interview.
- After the treatment.
- Well, we'll do the interview later.
Sorry, later.
You both can change
once your injuries are mended.
Okay. Disinfect it.
Don't worry. It won't hurt anymore,
okay?
Mister, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
I'm okay too.
Hmm.
Why is your hand like that?
I can't remember.
I think I was with my daughter.
Well, um, aren't you remembering now?
When I see this scar on my hand,
it's as if I can hear a child crying.
Though, she might not
make it through today.
My daughter, that is.
What's your daughter's name?
Yoon Hee.
"Yoon Hee."
But I'm here, so it'll work out.
I'm the cure, right? A human cure.
All right, the treatment is done.
Excellent. Thank you.
All right. Why don't you put these on?
Ha-na, you should get changed as well,
after Mr. Carter is done.
Once you arrive in North Korea,
your mission will be finished.
I sincerely hope
that the cure is completed in time,
so that your child can be saved.
Was this mission really my choice?
So that I could save my daughter?
You'll get an answer
to that question
once your mission is complete.
Until then, don't let down your guard.
Remember this.
There may even be individuals
on this plane who are after Ha-na.
Didn't you say
that the US can't interfere anymore?
We have reason to believe
that the CIA may have ordered
other forces to move in on Ha-na.
It's possible North-Korean personnel may
be involved, wanting to start a coup.
The CIA contacting
the spy organization makes sense,
but what do you mean
by a coup within North Korea?
Well, we suspect
the virus may have been spread,
by those who want
the current regime to collapse.
Until Ha-na is safely reunited
with her father Dr. Jung,
don't trust anybody.
Don't even trust me.
- What's going on?
- Don't worry. I'll go investigate.
- We've lost contact with the cockpit.
What?
- Director Kim, what's going on?
- Is there a problem?
Hurry, we need a medic!
What happened?
They both just collapsed.
But they just drank coffee.
Coffee?
Sir, I didn't do it.
Look, I brought the coffee
but that was it.
No,
you can't! Who else can fly the plane?
Look at his bloodshot eyes.
This plane's going down in ten minutes
if it's a mutated variant.
What do you think you're doing?
Director Kim tried to kill Comrade
Pilot and Comrade Assistant Pilot.
If we don't kill them, we will all die!
Everyone, calm down.
First we'll confirm they're infected.
Medic!
How does it look?
Technically,
in normal situations, this level
wouldn't be considered high enough,
but considering
the altitude and cabin pressure,
technically, this is an infection.
So, are they infected or not?
Give us more time to observe it.
At least give us five minutes
to get a proper reading.
What's the difference
in killing them now or then?
Hang on. But his hair roots are strong.
Don't you know it's too late
once the hair starts falling out?
The protocol states that
reading times are to be observed.
If anything happens in the meantime,
they will instantly be shot.
Open the blinds in the cabin!
The blinds, they aren't working.
Why is the medical room
emergency lights off?
Out of my way.
- Move!
- Director Kim!
Director Kim, what's the situation?
Due to what felt like
extreme turbulence,
we appear to have lost power on board.
Now, that is an extremely...
Carter.
Only you can hear what I'm saying.
In the cargo compartment,
I am sensing the heat signatures
of what appear to be an adult and Ha-na.
- The cargo compartment?
- You need to head there.
- Let's go.
- This is why South Korean bastards...
- You can never trust them.
- Ha-na!
CARGO COMPARTMENT
CABIN
Ha-na. Are you okay? Who did this?
Why are you doing this?
Your eyes really say
that you don't remember anything.
- What?
- Yeah. Yeah.
If you don't remember anything,
at least you'll be at peace
when you die, right?
Carter.
Director Kim.
Why... Why are you doing this?
Ri Cheol Ju, you son of a bitch!
Ha-na, are you all right?
- Yes.
- Don't move!
Who is it?
Who's the head of the North Korean coup?
Who spread this virus? Who created it!?
Do you really think North Korea would
make this mess just to die
and when we don't
even have a vaccine yet?
But have you considered that maybe,
it's the South that wanted the coup?
I guess you,
are just another facet of this
to make it more interesting.
Now that's enough of your bullshit.
Just answer me.
Who is it?
Lee Dong Jin?
Han Seol Ho?
Kim Jong Hyeok?
Director Kim.
You're embarrassing yourself,
You believe those stereotypes, huh?
You think I have loyalty to the North?
What, 'cause I'm from North Korea?
Is that it then?
What?
Do you think there's only one spy
like him in the North?
Ri Cheol Ju, you asshole!
Are you working with the United States?
Listen carefully.
Up there in the North,
the people call South Korea
an American colony.
The thing is,
after having met these Americans,
it looks like being on their side,
is more than worth it for me.
America.
Its freedom and equality.
A place with wealth
and all its opportunity.
Considering all of that!
Even if I live one day!
I'll live free, like a human!
Do you get that, Director?
Do you?
Die, you son of a bitch!
Ha-na, get out of here.
Mister.
Run fast and get help.
Hurry up! Be quick!
- What's going on here?
- Huh?
Wasn't that an explosion?
- The cockpit door won't open.
- What?
Ha-na!
- Ha-na. You all right?
- Why were you in there?
Have you been down
there this whole time?
What were you doing in there?
Hey, wait a sec.
Director Kim went
that way. Was he there?
He's dead.
The North Korean guy...
he killed Mr. Kim.
What's going on? What are you people
trying to pull over here?
We... We don't know anything!
Who was it? Who killed Director Kim?
Could you recognize their face?
It's okay.
It was that man!
Did you kill Director Kim? Huh?
Answer the question!
Yes, I did.
It was me.
Listen, Director Kim was just a CIA spy
that was planted here.
He was trying to take Ha-na away.
So I did it. I killed him.
I knew those South Korean bastards
would do this!
They're working with the CIA.
Those bastards!
Are you really going to listen
to this bastard?
Hey, hey, hey. Whoa! Calm down, okay?
Put the guns away for a second.
You can't just accept
whatever this guy is trying to say.
Ask Ha-na.
Is that true, Ha-na?
Did Director Kim take you?
Oh, yes, Comrade Sun Hwa.
Are you all right?
How are the pilot
and the co-pilot doing?
They are...
doing just fine.
He's choking her. One of
the North Koreans is choking Ha-na.
He's... He's covering
himself in her blood.
It's Ha-na's blood.
The infected aren't attacking him
because of her blood.
Ah! This is so exciting.
Hey. Look at you trying to survive.
This is some thrill, huh?
Looks like the people's hero,
is just a human when faced with death.
Get ready!
Moving to an estimated landing point
at 40 degrees latitude
and 124 degrees longitude.
- Ha-na, are you all right?
- Yes.
Kill the man
and catch the girl alive!
Somebody is on my tail!
They're
probably working with Ri Cheol Ju.
Carter!
Carter, are you all right?
Answer me. Carter!
Ha-na, grab the steering wheel! Go!
Okay.
Shoot the wheel!
Shit!
I'm out of bullets!
Move the car closer! Faster! More! More!
Where do I go now?
If you follow the valley down
about 20 meters,
there's a cliff and a rope bridge.
We are moving
to the opposite side now too.
The mission will be complete
once you get there.
Mister.
Here.
Let's go.
- Be careful, it's slippery.
- Okay.
Here. Get on my back.
I can go on my own.
Hug my neck
and clasp your hands together!
Don't ever let go!
Okay.
Carter!
Are you okay?
Are you Han Jung Hee?
Ha-na, are you okay?
So you're Ha-na. You've done a lot.
Thank you for your hard work.
Now we can leave together.
What exactly are you saying?
Leave together?
This is simply incredible.
A job well done.
It's a surprise
that you would love a woman
and a daughter that you two had
while you were working undercover. Hmm?
And I applaud you
for putting your life at risk,
to protect your own daughter.
Who are you, huh?
Oh.
I'm Kim Jong Hyeok.
You know, seeing what you're capable of,
you sure don't seem
like you lost your memory.
Stop laughing. I want my memory back.
Go on. Sit down.
Once the device implanted
in your ear is removed,
you'll get your memory back.
Trust me. Okay?
I'm going to open
the stitches. This will hurt a bit.
Mister!
What's going on? Lieutenant General!
Get up!
- Carter!
- Mister!
Mister!
Where are you taking Carter? Tell me.
Look here, Han Jung Hee.
Don't make a scene. And stand down.
But you made us a promise!
We could leave this country
after Carter had finished the mission.
That deal was between you and the party.
I have never made such a promise.
Then what does that mean?
Put her in the car.
Let go of me. Let go!
Let go!
What do you think you're doing with me?
Love.
I always feel sad when I hear that word.
What is it to be so cruel?
Who knew that comrade Han Jung Hee,
the most competent
female comrade in the North,
could now find herself struggling
down in the gutter?
Huh?
Look, just make your point.
I knew it from the first moment,
the virus spread.
This completely rotten country,
all those pricks in South Korea
who only think about money,
and even those arrogant
American imperialist bastards,
can be destroyed in one strike.
It's a once in a lifetime chance
from the heavens.
Wait, are you
the head of the coup in the North?
Comrade Han.
Listen to me.
Let's create a new world together.
Hey, the bastard's awake.
You American traitor.
So you're finally awake.
Where are you taking me?
Just keep quiet,
and your wife will make the decision.
My wife?
If you had never shown up here,
then the Comrade First Lieutenant Han
who I once loved
just might have been my wife.
Go on.
Get out.
Move it, pal. What are you looking at?
Enjoy that breath. It'll be your last.
Who knows, huh?
You might walk away a North Korean hero
and ex spy agent,
or you might become
barbecue in this fire.
Don't worry though,
it'll be decided soon.
Comrade hero,
if you've been good to your wife,
you might live.
Please let me live.
Pick up the phone.
Put it on speaker.
Yeah.
Where is Carter?
Waiting to be thrown
into the pit.
- What's the order?
- Wait a bit longer.
Yes, sir.
Kim Jong Hyeok, tell me where he is.
He's at, uh, the Sinuiju
Chemical Factory's biochemical facilities
about 1.5 kilometers to the north..
I'M GOING TO CALL YOU
KEEP ME ON THE PHONE - CARTER
You look like
you still haven't decided.
Don't overthink it.
You need to save your family,
Carter, yourself, and your daughter.
I can guarantee their safety.
Let us go, like the party had promised.
I don't care what you do here,
what you do with North Korea.
Well, maybe you should care.
For instance,
if you two work with the Americans
and were to say all sorts of bullshit
to the entire world,
how will I look?
I'll most likely get furious
and drag you all here again
to bury you all deep within
that anthrax incinerator.
But then again...
...if Carter Lee,
who saved the North from the virus,
were to stand with me and my men,
your husband will become a new idol
in uniting all of North Korea.
Idol, huh?
You just want a puppet, don't you,
who will do as you please?
Look, if it means he survives
then being a puppet is a small price.
Am I wrong?
Lieutenant General.
As I'm looking at you, threatening me
that you'll kill my husband,
I'm not seeing
any new world
for the North Korean people.
I was certain you'd
been blinded by a man,
but you've been blinded
to your immediate future as well.
I can't plan the future
of the People's Republic
with someone who's as blind as you are.
Shoot him!
Get down!
This is the room. Yoon Hee is in here.
- Where is she?
- Huh? No, where is she?
This has to be the right room.
No, don't!
- This child...
- She's our daughter!
She's our daughter?
Carter!
Mister!
Ha-na.
It's all right.
These people are just researchers.
Doctor, our daughter...
You've been infected as well.
The child will be conscious
in about half an hour.
We need to get out of here, now.
Please save my Ha-na.
The door is locked.
Ha-na, it's me.
Ha-na. Ha-na, let's go.
Go into the closet
in front of you.
Give her to me.
Seven minutes ago, a train operated
by the... the Chinese government
left Ryung Gye for Dandong,
carrying the infected.
Not even the North Korean government
can interfere with that train,
so we need to stop it.
But we need to get
your memory back first.
Doctor.
If you open his stitches,
you'll see a device.
If you plug this into it,
his memories will return.
"BD-7."
- Do you think it is wise for...
- Yoon Hee!
- Dad...
- I'll get Ha-na to the North.
Dr. Jung is with me at the moment.
Yoon Hee's been infected.
Just a bit longer. We're almost there.
Jung Hee!
The country is falling into ruins
because of the virus.
So do you think it wise
that our Comrade hero of the Republic
is abandoning the country
during a time such as this?
Let us go. I beg you.
Lieutenant General, please.
Just let us go, please.
So you still haven't come
to your senses, Comrade.
Have you forgotten
that having your child
was the party's decision?
Please tell your superiors
if you... if you swear
to release our family,
I'll get Ha-na to the North.
Do you know what you've said?
What it will do
to you, your daughter, and your wife?
No one knows specifically
if the CIA moved Ha-na out already,
or if she's still hidden somewhere
in South Korea.
I can find her if I become bait
and approach the CIA on my own.
I don't side with the North or America,
so it won't be an
international conflict.
How can I trust you'll do it though,
an agent who got plastic surgery
to spy for seven years?
If you run, and abandon
your wife and your daughter,
that will only mean exposure
of our entire operation.
Then, um...
BD-7 can erase everything that I know.
Use it and send me South.
Carter.
BD-7.
How do you know that information?
Just give us this one chance.
And I'll get Ha-na
to the North, you'll see.
In exchange, you let us go.
- Yoon Hee!
- No!
- Yoon Hee! Yoon Hee!
- Yoon Hee!
- Yoon Hee.
Comrade Carter.
You must successfully
see this thing through.
Because now...
...Yoon Hee's been infected.
Yoon Hee. Yoon Hee.
No.
Yoon Hee.
Oh, my baby.
Have your memories come back?
Do you... Do you remember us?
I'm sorry.
I left you here.
You went to save our family.
And well...
And you really did.
Carter!
Listen. Take the children first and run!
Ha-na, quickly.
If you move northwest,
you'll see a train coming in.
Just hurry.
What about you though?
Just worry about the children now.
- Doctor. Hurry!
- Hold on, Ha-na!
Ha-na, you have to hold on tight!
Hide behind the car.
Ha-na, hang on tight!
DANDONG EMERGENCY MEDICAL COMMAND CENTER
Ha-na. Stay right here.
No! Get away from me!
Prepare to fire.
Go lower. Go lower!
Hang on, Ha-na! Ha-na!
Ha-na! Take my hand!
You sneaky shit.
So,
you think those memories
you finally regained
are memories that are really yours?
Doctor, get on before me!
- Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee, are you all right?
Do you recognize me?
M-Mom.
Yes, it's me.
Where are we going now?